<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Document>
	<Source>http://www.bspcn.com/2007/11/26/5-best-things-to-say-when-caught-sleeping-at-your-desk/</Source>
	<Topic>
    5 Best Things to Say When Caught Sleeping at Your Desk
  </Topic>
	<Style>
		<BackgroundColor>#000000</BackgroundColor>
		<Color>#00ff00</Color>
		<HoverColor>#ffff00</HoverColor>
	</Style>
	<Count>6</Count>
	<Content>
    5. “They told me at the Blood Bank this might happen.”

    4. “This is just a 15 minute power nap they raved about in the time management course you sent me to.”

    3. “Whew! Guess I left the top off the Whiteout. You probably got here just in time.”

    2. “Did you ever notice sound coming out of these keyboards when you put your ear down real close?” And the NUMBER ONE best thing to say if you get caught sleeping at your desk…

    1. Raise your head slowly and say, “…in Jesus’ name, Amen.”

    25. “Oh, Man! Come in at 6 in the morning and look what happens!”

    24. “This is one of the seven habits of highly effective people!”

    23. “This is in exchange for the six hours last night when I dreamed about work!”

    22. “You don’t discriminate against those with Latient Atrophy Zymosis Yeast syndrome, DO YOU?!?”

    21. “Gee, I thought you (the boss) were gone for the day.”

    20. “They told me at the blood bank this might happen.”

    19. “Oh, Hi, I was trying to pick up my contact lens without my hands.”

    18. “This is just a 15 minute power-nap like they raved about in the last time management course you sent me to.”

    17. “Whew! Guess I left the top off the liquid paper”

    16. “I was just meditating on the mission statement and envisioning a new paradigm!”

    15. “This is one of the seven habits of highly effective people!”

    14. “I was testing the keyboard for drool resistance”

    13. “I’m doing the “Stress Level Elimination Exercise Plan” (SLEEP) I learned at the last mandatory seminar you made me attend.”

    12. “It worked well for Reagan, didn’t it?”

    11. “This is a highly specific Yoga position to relieve work-related stress.”

    10. “Just pacing myself for the all-nighter tonight!”

    9. “I was working smarter-not harder.”

    8. “Auggh! Why did you interrupt me? I had almost figured out a solution to our biggest problem.”

    7. “I’m in the management training program.”

    6. “The coffee machine is broken….”

    5. “Someone must’ve put decaf in the wrong pot.”

    4. “Boy, that cold medicine I took last night just won’t wear off!”

    3. “Ah, the unique and unpredictable circadian rhythms of the workaholic!”

    2. “It’s okay… I’m still billing the client.”

    1. “…and I especially thank you for my excellent boss, Amen!”
  </Content>
</Document>