<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Document>
	<Source>http://www.bspcn.com/2008/07/07/50-greatest-quotes-on-men/</Source>
	<Topic>
    50 Greatest Quotes on Men
  </Topic>
	<Style>
		<BackgroundColor>#000000</BackgroundColor>
		<Color>#00ff00</Color>
		<HoverColor>#ffff00</HoverColor>
	</Style>
	<Count>6</Count>
	<Content>
     I never liked the men I loved and never loved the men I liked. ~ Fanny Brice
    


     You can tell the strength of a nation by the women behind its men. ~ Benjamin Disraeli
    


    

    Power does not corrupt men; fools, however, if they get into a position of power, corrupt power. ~ George Bernard Shaw
    


     When men and woman die, as poets sung, his heart’s the last part moves, her last, the tongue. ~ Benjamin Franklin
    


     Passion makes idiots of the cleverest men, and makes the biggest idiots clever. ~ Francois de La Rochefoucauld
    


     If you would convince a man that he does wrong, do right. Men will believe what they see. ~ Henry David Thoreau
    


    



    All men’s miseries derive from not being able to sit in a quiet room alone. ~ Blaise Pascal
    


     The world judge of men by their ability in their profession, and we judge of ourselves by the same test: for it is on that on which our success in life depends. ~ William Hazlitt
    


     All women become like their mothers. That is their tragedy. No man does. That’s his. ~ Oscar Wilde
    


     God made woman beautiful and foolish; beautiful, that man might love her; and foolish, that she might love him. ~ Unknown
    


     Young men want to be faithful, and are not; old men want to be faithless, and cannot. ~ Oscar Wilde
    


     It’s not the men in my life that counts, it’s the life in my men. ~ Mae West
    


     A man may conquer a million men in battle but one who conquers himself is, indeed, the greatest of conquerors. ~ Buddha
    


     Women need a reason to have sex. Men just need a place. ~ Billy Crystal
    


     Men play the game; women know the score. ~ Roger Woddis
    


     Man will occasionally stumble over the truth, but most times he will pick himself up and carry on. ~ Winston Churchill
    


     There are some sluggish men who are improved by drinking; as there are fruits that are not good until they are rotten. ~ Samuel Johnson
    


     When a man points a finger at someone else, he should remember that four of his fingers are pointing at himself. ~ Louis Nizer
    


    



    Happy is he who still loves something he loved in the nursery: He has not been broken in two by time; he is not two men, but one, and he has saved not only his soul but his life. ~ Gilbert K. Chesterton
    


     Few men have been admired of their familiars. ~ Michel de Montaigne
    


     Boys will be boys, and so will a lot of middle-aged men. ~ Kin Hubbard
    


     If it’s true that men are such beasts, this must account for the fact that most women are animal lovers. ~ Doris Day
    


     All men [are] of one metal, but not in one mold. ~ John Lyly
    


     Men are like steel. When they lose their temper, they lose their worth. ~ Chuck Norris
    


    

    Adversity makes men, and prosperity makes monsters. ~ Victor Hugo
    


     Men seldom, or rather never for a length of time and deliberately, rebel against anything that does not deserve rebelling against. ~ Thomas Carlyle
    


    

    Is it not rather what we expect in men, that they should have numerous strands of experience lying side by side and never compare them with each other? ~ George Eliot
    


     A child, from the time he can think, should think about all he sees, should suffer for all who cannot live with honesty, should work so that all men can be honest, and should be honest himself. ~ Jose Marti
    


     The greatest truths are the simplest, and so are the greatest men. ~ Julius Charles Hare
    


     Men are so willing to respect anything that bores them. ~ Marilyn Moroe
    


     There are more men ennobled by study than by nature. ~ Marcus Tullius Cicero
    


     Young men preen. Old men scheme. ~ Mason Cooley
    


     If you want anything said, ask a man. If you want something done, ask a woman. ~ Margaret Thatcher
    


     A diplomat is a man who always remembers a woman’s birthday but never remembers her age. ~ Robert Frost
    


     Classical quotation is the parole of literary men all over the world. ~ Samuel Johnson
    


     Men do not quit playing because they grow old; they grow old because they quit playing. ~ Oliver Wendell Holmes
    


     The desire of excessive power caused the angels to fall; the desire of knowledge caused men to fall. ~ Francis Bacon
    


     Perfect friendship is the friendship of men who are good, and alike in excellence; for these wish well alike to each other qua good, and they are good in themselves. ~ Aristotle
    


     Men should be like Kleenex, soft, strong and disposable. ~ Cher
    


     There are three kinds of men. The one that learns by reading. The few who learn by observation. The rest of them have to pee on the electric fence for themselves. ~ Will Rogers
    


     Priests are not men of the world; it is not intended that they should be; and a University training is the one best adapted to prevent their becoming so. ~ Samuel Butler
    


     Let me embrace thee, sour adversity, for wise men say it is the wisest course. ~ William Shakespeare
    


     Men are only as great as they are kind. ~ Elbert Hubbard
    


     Men kick friendship around like a football, but it doesn’t seem to crack. Women treat it like glass and it goes to pieces. ~ Anne Morrow Lindbergh
    


     Only the wisest and stupidest of men never change. ~ Confucius
    


     In the long run, men hit only what they aim at. Therefore, they had better aim at something high. ~ Henry David Thoreau
    


     It is a fact often observed, that men have written good verses under the inspiration of passion, who cannot write well under other circumstances. ~ Ralph Waldo Emerson
    


     If there is no struggle, there is no progress. Those who profess to favor freedom, and deprecate agitation, are men who want crops without plowing up the ground, they want rain without thunder and lightning. ~ Frederick Douglass
    


     Violent men have not been known in history to die to a man. They die up to a point. ~ Mohandas Gandhi
    


     Great men or men of great gifts you shall easily find, but symmetrical men never. ~ Ralph Waldo Emerson
  </Content>
</Document>